grammar.cl 2019-04-01

# Privacy Policy

## www.grammar.cl

Grammar.cl is committed to ensuring your privacy is protected. Any information that you provide to Grammar.cl by which you can be identified will be used only in accordance with the privacy policy stated below.

**Non-personal Information:**  
In some cases, information that is not personally identifiable may be automatically collected and/or logged. For example, information about the visitor's browser, operating system, IP address, and the domain name of sites that are linked to the Grammar.cl web base because it allows Grammar.cl to accommodate the needs of the majority of visitors. It also assists with troubleshooting and diagnoses if there are problems with servers, and the information helps produce important statistics on how often pages are visited. Finally, this information can be used in the detection of security breaches and the safeguarding of Grammar.cl computing resources.

**Cookies:**  
The viewer may receive a cookie. A cookie is a small data structure sent from a web server to the internet browser and saved on your hard drive as a text file. Most web browsers are set to accept cookies. If you do not wish to receive cookies you can disable this function in your web browser although doing so may restrict access to some web pages.

Cookies store non-personal information such as your server address, your top level domain name, the date and the time of your visit to the site, the pages you accessed and downloaded, the address of the last site you visited, and the type of browser you are using. We use this information for monitoring our web site use to facilitate web site management, development and planning. We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes.

The only self identifying information involved in the cookies shows the general location where you come from, helping us to track which countries use the website to the greatest extent.

**Personal Information:**   
All personal information that is collected is done so directly from you. All information given to us by you is used only for the purposes you state at the time and for internal management.

No other third party will have access to your information. We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information at any time except in the situation of your consent; our explanation beforehand; it is required or authorized by law; it will prevent or lessen a serious and imminent threat to somebody's life or health or; the disclosure is reasonably necessary for law enforcement or for the protection of public revenue.

**Security:**  
While Grammar.cl takes measures to ensure privacy of all information transmitted on the website, Grammar.cl is unable to guarantee secure transmission of information over the internet. Viewers must be aware of the risks they are taking in any information that they choose to submit to any website or in electronic mail. If the viewer is concerned with transmitting information over the internet the viewer may contact Grammar.cl by telephone.

**Links:**  
Grammar.cl is in no way responsible for websites that are linked from Grammar.cl, once you leave the Grammar.cl jurisdiction we are unable to ensure your privacy. The protection policies of the other website in question may vary greatly from that of Grammar.cl.

**Changes:**   
Changes may be made at any time according to our privacy policy. Changes will become effective immediately upon changes to this website. Viewers may check this website at anytime to be up to date on the privacy policies of Grammar.cl.

Effective Date: 01 November 2007
